const questions = [
    {
        question: "The term ‘Computer’ is derived from?",
        correct: 0,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Latin' },
            { 1: 'German' },
            { 2: 'French' },
            { 3: 'Arabic' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "The basic operations performed by a computer are?",
        correct: 3,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Arithmetic Operation' },
            { 1: 'Logical Operation' },
            { 2: 'Storage and relative' },
            { 3: 'All of the Above' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "What visual representation does Resource Monitor use when information is filtered?",
        correct: 3,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'A red filter label' },
            { 1: 'A green highlight' },
            { 2: 'An exclamation point' },
            { 3: 'An Orange Bar' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "After you install the NLB feature, what management tool is available from Server Manager?",
        correct: 0,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'NLB Manager' },
            { 1: 'Windows Update' },
            { 2: 'Storage Manager' },
            { 3: 'Cluster Manager' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "What is the footprint of the VHD for Nano Server Datacenter Edition?",
        correct: 3,
        answers: [
            { 0: '1 GB' },
            { 1: '2.4 GB' },
            { 2: '4.6 GB' },
            { 3: '509 MB' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "How much space does a VHDX support?",
        correct: 1,
        answers: [
            { 0: '8 TB' },
            { 1: '64 TB' },
            { 2: '2 TB' },
            { 3: '1 TB' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "What PowerShell command deletes a container?",
        correct: 1,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Delete-Container' },
            { 1: 'Remove-Container' },
            { 2: 'Erase-Container' },
            { 3: 'Scrub-Container' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which virtual switch type permits communication between the VMs on the host and between the VMs and the host itself?",
        correct: 0,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'Internal' },
            { 1: 'Private' },
            { 2: 'Shielded' },
            { 3: 'Firewall' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which command is used to set terminal IO characteristic?",
        correct: 3,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'tty' },
            { 1: 'ctty' },
            { 2: 'ptty' },
            { 3: 'stty' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which command is used to record a user login session in a file",
        correct: 2,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'macro' },
            { 1: 'read' },
            { 2: 'script' },
            { 3: 'none' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which command is used to display the operating system name",
        correct: 3,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'os' },
            { 1: 'kernel' },
            { 2: 'unix' },
            { 3: 'uname' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which command is used to display the unix version",
        correct: 0,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'uname -r' },
            { 1: 'uname -n' },
            { 2: 'uname -t' },
            { 3: 'kernel' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which command is used to print a file",
        correct: 2,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'print' },
            { 1: 'ptr' },
            { 2: 'lpr' },
            { 3: 'none' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Using which command you find resource limits to the session?",
        correct: 1,
        answers: [
            { 0: 'rlimit' },
            { 1: 'ulimit' },
            { 2: 'setrlimit' },
            { 3: 'getrlimit' },
        ]
    },
    {
        question: "Which option of ls command used to view file inode number",
        correct: 2,
        answers: [
            { 0: '-l' },
            { 1: '-o' },
            { 2: '-i' },
            { 3: '-p' },
        ]
    },
]


export default questions